rvnl.org 2008-06-17

# Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd.

At Rail Vikas Nigam Limited we take your right to privacy very seriously. Please read on for more details about our Privacy Policy. 

**What information do we collect when you browse our Site?**  
We collect information that you submit to us (such as your name, posting address or email address and other information from which your identity is discernible) when you use our Site. We also use "cookies" on the Site. A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your computer from the computers used by a website. We use cookies to monitor your use of the Site and to tailor your experience of the Site so that it best suits you. Most browsers allow you to accept or reject all cookies or to notify you when they are sent. If you reject cookies, this may affect your use of the Site. 

**How do we use that information?**  
We will use your personal information for the purpose for which you provided it (e.g. sending email newsletters). We may also send your information to other people (including people based outside of the India which may have less strict rules about processing your information) if that is a necessary part of the reason for which you sent it to us (e.g. asking a company to provide a quotation, or to distribute your CV), or if we believe the law requires it. We may aggregate your personal information with other data (so that you cannot be identified) and use that aggregated data for administrative purposes and/or share it with other people. We would like to use your personal information you supply to us to: 

  * Send you information from time to time about Rail Vikas Nigam Limited and the fields in which we operate which we think may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information to contact you in this way, please email us at [info@rvnl.org](mailto:info@rvnl.org)
  * Share your details with other Railway Public Sector Undertakings. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please email us at [info@rvnl.org](mailto:info@rvnl.org)
  * (c) Share your details with third parties who offer products and services in which we think you may be interested. If you do not want us to use your information to contact you in this way, please email us at [info @rvnl.org](mailto:info@rvnl.org). 

If at any time you would like us to remove your information or change it because it is incorrect, please contact us at [info@rvnl.org](mailto:info@rvnl.org) . Please note that if you post any of your personal information in the public areas of the Site, such as in online bulletin boards, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in the public areas of the Site. You may submit feedback to us and if you choose to do so, we may use such feedback as if it were our property including using it for marketing purposes. We may contact you for further information on your feedback. 

**Links**  
Our Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of it when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information from them. This privacy policy applies solely to the information collected on this Site. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect from them, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose this information to third parties. If at any point we decide that we wish to use personally identifiable information collected from our users in a manner that differs from that stated at the time this information was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice whether or not to consent to our using their personal information in accordance with our updated privacy policy.
